INSTRUCTIONS

You choose to be either archer or shooter hero (they differ by range and damage).  In the beginning you have 3 lives and shooting range 3 or 5 (depending on the hero). You walk in a maze inhabited by enemies of yours using the arrow keys, you shoot with space bar. You enter the next level when you kill all of the enemies. Every enemy killed gives score of 100. You can collect bonuses.

CONTROLS:
Left arrow - move left
Right arrow - move right
Up arrow - move up
Down arrow - move down
Space bar - shoot

BONUSES
Gold - 50 points
Diamond - 100 points
Harth - extra life
D - extra damage
R - extra range

Press escape to go back to start menu.


